Mitchell Zilberg

Web and multimedia developer who excels in a team environment and under the pressure of strict deadlines. A former broadcast media and multimedia specialist who plans to incorporate my project-based work experience into the tech industry.

Education

CareerFoundry, Online — Full-Stack Web Development October 2020 - PRESENT

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON — Television-Broadcasting April 2020

John Abbott College, Montreal, QC — *Media Arts & Literature* December 2017

Projects

Pokedex: Front-end Javascript application

Communicates with an external API to display a list of pokemon.

MyFlix App: Full-stack React & Node application

Displays a list of movies, allows users to register and personalize their own list of favourite movies by communicating with a DIY API.

Chat App: React Native mobile application

Lets users enter a chat room to communicate with their friends.

Work Experience

Senior Photographer- Lifetouch Canada, ON & QC

October 2020 - Present

Set up and wrap equipment, photograph up to 200 kids per day. Train and supervise new photographers.

Supervisor, Show Producer, Box Office, & Bartender- Absolute

Comedy, Ottawa, ON

March 2017 - January 2020

Hired, trained, made weekly schedules for, and supervised doormen. Booked reservations over the phone (Microsoft Excel), handled complaints, and checked-in customers while working the box office.

Grip & Camera Operator- MATV, Gatineau, QC

June 2019 - January 2020

Set up, wrapped, and operated industry standard television camera & audio equipment.

Director, Shooter, & Editor-TVC Basse-Lievre, Gatineau, QC

June 2019 - September 2019

Directed, shot, and edited a four-part series on community events that took place during the summer of 2019 in the Basse-Lievre region.

Ottawa, Ontario (613) 618-2496 mzilbergdeveloper@gmail.com

Linkedin, Github, & Portfolio

https://bit.ly/39Hu7rc

https://github.com/mitche <u>Ilzilberg</u>

https://mitchellzilberg.gith ub.io/portfolio-website/

Tools (* = some experience)

HTML

CSS. SCSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript ES6

DOM manipulation

jQuery

Git, Github & Version Control

Ajax

React.is

Redux

React Native

Node.is

Express.js

NPM

RESTful Api's

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

Angular*

TypeScript*

AWS*

Adobe Premiere Davinci Resolve Microsoft Word / Excel

Adobe After Effects*

Adobe Audition*

Photoshop*

Skills

Bilingual in French & English.

Test driven development approach.

Experienced with a project-based work load.